

Robert Cereghini, Web Developer

480.444.9873

DETAILS

480.444.9873

rcereghini@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/robert-

cereghini-20a402149/

PROFILE

Front-End Web Developer with knowledge in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, React Native, Redux, Python, C# and more. Digital Marketing and Copywriting experience. Displays the ability to learn new skills and employ a heightened attention to detail. Typically expands responsibilities beyond the initial job requirements. Regarded as a strong problem solver.

Visit rcereghini.github.io to view project samples and online course history!

SKILLS

LINKS

LinkedIn

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

React

React Native

Redux

Node.js

Python

Django

MySQL/PostgreSQL

C#

Angular

Unity

Copywriting

Photoshop/Illustrator/InDesign

Social Media Ads

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Jr. Web Developer, Petroleum Rx, LLC

Oct 2018 - Present, Tempe, Arizona

Front-End Development w/ Angular

Full-Stack Developer Intern, Neureka

Jun 2018 - Sep 2018

Part-time Full-Stack development using Python/Django and React Native.

Digital Marketing and Communications, Clear Title Agency of Arizona

Apr 2017 – Oct 2018, Phoenix, Arizona

WordPress development, Salesforce customization, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Facebook Ads, Social Media, Copywriting, Adobe Photoshop/Illustrator/InDesign, Process Automation, SEO, Client Services. Developed several webpages, improved daily operation w/ automations, found in-house replacements for third party services.

Substitute Teacher, Delta T

Jan 2016 - Apr 2017, Phoenix, AZ

Long term positions at STEM (Science, Technology, Engineering, Mathematics) schools.

EDUCATION

Lynda, Udemy, SoloLearn, freeCodeCamp, egghead.io, and many online docs!

Oct 2016 - Oct 2018

Arizona State University, Bachelor of Interdisciplinary Studies

2012, Tempe, AZ